

# **Antreas** PAPADOPOULO

JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER

antreas.paps@yahoo.com

+44 7999 435 635

www.inthemaking.tech



## About Me



Fresh out of the university searching for the first step into my technological career. My latest interest is design and animation of scalable vector graphics using Adobe Illustrator and After Effects and their integration into web designing and development using CSS and Javascript.

I understand I do not have much experience but I am trying to make up to that with personal projects to keep my skills sharp and add new ones. I keep up to date with the latest trends, and I always have an open minded approach to everything. Hence why my dissertation was based on decentralised, distributed networks.

My last complete project was my personal website created using Laravel, as a means • of showing what I am capable of doing with my current experience. I started using GitHub for personal projects and work as it is a mean for potential employers to have a look at my work, as well as for people to perhaps get infuenced from my work.

My current project is an attempt to create a simple and minimalistic, yet fully functional Project/Task Management System to help a client with managing their workload and improving their efficiency; other available options are either too complex or non-affordable for small teams with a strict budget.

## Work Experience -



### Junior Web Developer| zzDot | September 2018 - Now

- > Redesigning and developing the company's website
- > Providing alternatives on client suggested website templates
- > Assisting in back-end bug finding, error handling, testing
- > Learning new frameworks including Vue.js
- > Brainstorming solutions to client problems with a group of Senior Developers

#### Student AV Support | University of Liverpool | March 2018 - June 2018

- > Providing technical support using University systems/equipment
- > Daily check of University equipment and computers
- > Responsible for the maintenance and upgrade of certain building equipment
- > Aimed to improve the teaching experience to both the lecturers and the students

#### Private Company IT Trainee | ComNetCom | July 2016

- > Assisted on everyday issues regarding personal computers and servers
- > Completion of custom computer builds

#### Summer Staff | PricewaterHouse Coopers | August 2015

- > Aided in the maintenance and update of client files
- > Shadowed a PwC partner in his daily routines
- > Assisted around the office on a daily basis with tasks including book keeping

#### Military Service | Republic of Cyprus | June 2013 - July 2015

- > Two year military service as a Special Forces Commando
- > Worked in a select team to carry out drills and practice scenarios
- > Taught to be guick on my feet and think outside the box
- > Overcme mental and physical obstacles

## Education ——



### **Bachelor in Computer Science**

#### Univeristy of Liverpool

Thesis Project (First class):

> Decentralized Rental Agreement based on Smart Contracts and Blockchains

#### Year 3 [Lower Second Class]:

> Software Engineering II | Efficient Sequential Algorithm | Technologies for E-Commerce

#### Year 2 Modules [Upper Second Class]:

> Scripting Languages | Advanced Object Oriented Programming | Artificial Intelligence

#### Year 1 Modules [First class]:

> Human-Centric Computing | Operating System Concepts

## Skills & Frameworks -



#### **Current/Active** Laravel

> HTML | Css | PHP | JavaScript

> Vector Design/Animation

#### Remix

#### Previously worked with Atom(Text Editor)

>C | C++

#### Adope Illustrator/After Effects

> Solidity

#### **Eclipse**

>Java

## **Databases**

>MySQL

## Languages





## Hobbies -



- Exploring new locations >
- Researching upcoming technologies
- Trading crypotocurrencies
- Dancing Salsa
- Extreme Sports Skydiving